(Author: Gosho Aoyama)
(Karya: Aoyama Gosho) Wah, tingginya!
(Detective Conan: Dimensional Sniper)
(Detective Conan: Dimensional Sniper)
Damn it, you're not getting away!
Tidak akan kubiarkan kau kabur!
(An impossible sniper case) One sniper case started it all.
(Insiden penembakan yang mustahil) Awalnya dimulai dari insiden penembakan.
FBI!
FBI!
(A sealed past) That was the door to the sealed past.
Itu adalah pintu dari masa lalu yang tersegel.
What?!
Wah!
So he was a sniper.
Lawan kita adalah penembak jitu.
If only Akai-san is still with us.
Andai saja ada Akai...
Sera-neechan, why are you here?
Kenapa kak Sera ada di sini?
Don't make such a face.
Jangan membuat wajah begitu.
(The mystery behind FBI Agent Shuichi Akai's murder) I'll protect you even if it'll cost me my life.
(Penyelidik FBI yang terbunuh, misteri Akai Shuuichi) Meski taruhannya nyawaku, aku akan melindungimu.
(Shu...) Shu...
(Shuu...) Shuu...
(Theme Song: Love Searchlight by Ko Shibasaki) What is the culprit's objective hidden behind the red laser?
(Lagu tema : Shibasaki Kou, Love Searchlight) Apa tujuan pelaku yang sembunyi dari pandangan?
Conan-kun...
Conan...
And then the second sniper case has finally happened.
Lalu, insiden penembakan kedua juga...
Looks like all of Tokyo is freaking out.
Seluruh Tokyo menjadi panik!
(A deadly countdown begins) If this is a countdown...
(Hitung mundur kematian yang sudah dimulai) Kalau ini adalah sebuah hitung mundur...
What do you mean?
Apa maksudmu?
(Special Guests: Sota Fukushi  Patrick Harlan)
(Tamu spesial: Fukushi Souta, Patrick Harlan)
Watch out!
Awas!
A FBI sniper that was supposed to have been murdered
Penembak jitu FBI yang seharusnya sudah mati.
(A forbidden truth is revealed) will now have his forbidden truth revealed!
Sekarang, kebenaran yang terlarang akan terungkap.
Where are you, Shinichi?
(Kebenaran terlarang yang terungkap) Dimana kau berada? Shinichi.
Run, Ran!
Larilah, Ran!
I'm counting on you, cool kid.
Aku mengandalkanmu, nak.
You're the only one left!
Hanya kau harapan kita.
No more games,
Waktu bermain sudah berakhir, tuan detektif.
(Detective Conan  Dimensional Sniper) Detective Conan The Movie: Dimensional Sniper.
Adaptasi film, Detective Conan: Dimensional Sniper.
(Shu-nii...) Shu-nii...
(Kakak Shuu...) Kakak Shuu...
It can't be!
Jangan-jangan!